Hello.
こんにちは
nice to meet you.
初 めまして
Sorry, I'm confusing it.
ごめんなさい、まわしちゃってるんですけど
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Well, this was an introduction from Mr. Wang.
あれ、ワンさんからの紹介の いや、
At Yai-san.
ヤイさんで
Ah, hello.
あー、こんにちは
It's cute.
かわいいね
It's so cute.
めちゃめちゃかわいいじゃん
How many?
いくつ?
Are you turning 19?
19にな るこっち?
19 You look really mature.
19 め ちゃくちゃ大人っぽいね
Have you been waiting a minute?
ちょっと待ってた?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Well then, hey, is the weather nice?
じゃあ、ちょっとさ、 天気もいいっすか?
Isn't the weather that good?
天気そんなに良くないっすか?
It's a bit human.
ちょっと人だね
Wait a minute, then how about we take a walk?
ちょっと、そしたらさ、 散歩しよっか?
good?
いい?
On a walk.
散歩で
Well, I wish there were food stalls.
で、なんかさ、 屋台とかあったらさ、
It's not like I'm going to eat around, though.
ちょっと食べ歩きじゃないけどさ、
Let's say something.
ちょっというのしていこうよ
I'm a little nervous.
ちょっと緊張してんなー
Isn't that true?
そんなことない?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Also to relieve tension.
緊張ほぐすためにもね
Let's go eat some food or go out for a while.
食べ歩きだったり、ちょっとしていこうか
Isn't it cold?
寒くない?
Is it a bit cold?
ちょっと寒い?
Yai-chan, how old are you now?
ヤイちゃん、今いくつなの?
I'm 18 now.
今、18です
18?
The year you turn 19?
19になる年?
Ah, that's right.
ああ、そうです
Well then, the coming-of-age ceremony will still be several years from now.
じゃあ、成人式は、 まだ、多来年とか
More to come?
多 来?
I see.
なるほどね
Oh, what about work?
え、仕事とかは?
Is it a job or a part-time job?
仕事っていうか、 バイト?
Do you have a part-time job?
バイトしてんの?
byte.
バイト
My part-time job is at a pub and a ramen shop.
バイトは、 居酒屋と、 ラーメン屋さん
Do you run an izakaya and a ramen shop?
居酒屋と、ラーメン屋さんやってんの?
Izakaya-san.
居酒屋さん
In a group?
集団で?
There's quite a bit in it.
結構入ってる
I feel like I'm working hard.
バリバリ働いちゃってる感じだ
I see.
なるほどね
What about your boyfriend?
彼氏は?
I don't have a boyfriend.
彼氏はいません
彼氏はいない
Has he ever made one?
彼、作ったことあるでしょ?
I've made one before, but it lasted that long.
作ったことはあるけど、 そんな長く続いて
Even though she's so cute, she can't have a boyfriend.
こんな可愛いのにさ、 彼氏できないってさ、
what?
なに?
What exactly is there?
正確に何はあるのかなんですか?
Is that so?
なのかな?
Isn't that the case?
そういうわけでもない?
I don't know.
わかんない
They just don't make it.
ただ作んないだけっていうね
That's a possibility.
その可能性もあるよね
Because it looks like it'll be done soon.
だってすぐできそうじゃん
Because it's cute.
可愛いから
If I didn't choose.
選ばなかったら
Ah, yes.
あ、 そう
Do you want to choose?
選びたいの?
What kind of men do you like?
どういう男性が好きなんですか?
Hey.
へぇー
I'm the type of person who does everything, so
なんか、うちが尽くしちゃうタイプだから、
There are people who will do more than me.
うち以上に尽くしてくれる人がいる
There are people who will do their best.
尽くしてくれる人がいる
There are a lot of them.
いっぱいいるよ
not present.
いない
It's just that I haven't had enough encounters yet.
まだ出会いが足りないということはね
If you were a clerk at a ramen shop or an izakaya,
ラーメン屋さんとさ、 居酒屋の店員だったら、
Both are a bit of food and drink.
どっちもちょっと飲食だからね
In other words, an encounter.
つまり出会いがね
You know what the job entails.
仕事内容は分かってるんだよね
Of this?
これの?
Yeah.
うん
Well, that's because I understand the job description.
それはさ、なんでさ、 仕事内容分かった上でさ、
This is how we're doing it now.
こうやって今、 やってるじゃん
Why all of a sudden?
なんでまた急に
Um, specialized tuition fees.
あのー、 専門の学費を
Oh, I'm a professional student now.
あ、今専門学生なんだ
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Tuition fees for professional students?
専門学生の学費を?
to save up.
を貯めるために
Ah, that's what it is.
あ、そういうことね
I see.
そっか
It's tough.
大変だね
It's tough, isn't it?
大変ですね
It would be better to make it there and let the man serve it.
そこ作って男に出させた方がいいね
If it's that cute, I'll give it to you.
そんだけかわいいんだったら、 出 してくれるよ
It's expensive.
高いもん
That's to save up for tuition fees for professional students.
それはさ、専門学生の 学費を貯めるために
What do you mean?
っていうこと?
Yes, to save up for next year's tuition.
そう、来年の学費を 貯めるために
Because it's every year.
1年ごとだから
That's right.
そうなんだ
Is there a profession you would like to have in the future?
将来成りたい職業ってある?
Ah, the nurse.
あー、看護師
Do you want to become a nurse?
看護師になりたいの?
She's a good woman.
いい女じゃん
Do you want to nurse?
看護したいの?
I want to nurse.
看護したい
I want to be a nurse, or rather, I want to be an emergency worker.
看護したいというか、 救急の方にしたい
To.
へ ー
I see.
そっか
That's it.
あれだね
It's a Japanese treasure.
日本の宝だね
It's a mirror.
鏡だな
鏡 だな
That's right.
そっかそっか
Lifesaving?
人命救助的な?
I guess so.
そうかな
I want to become a nurse who goes to emergency situations.
救急現場に行く 看護師さんになりたい
I see.
なるほどね
そっか
I see, it's nice weather.
そっか、いい天気だね
It suddenly started to clear up.
めちゃくちゃ急に 晴れだした
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Warm.
あったかい
Uncle, I love going for walks, after all.
おじさんさ、 や っぱり散歩好きだからさ、
Now that I'm this year, I often go for morning walks.
この年になったらさ、 朝の散歩ってよく行くんだけどさ、
Yai-chan won't go, and I won't be going in the morning.
やいちゃんは行かないし、 朝はいかないなー
Go for a walk during the day or at night.
お昼か夜、 散歩は行く
But, the style is nice.
だけどさ、 スタイルいいじゃん
What is that?
あれ、何?
That's pretty much it.
結構、 あれだよね
What do you mean by that?
そんな別に、 なんていうの?
He doesn't seem to have the personality to sit on a throne and ride a taxi.
王着してタクシー乗ったりとかっていう 性格でもなさそうだ
But.
けど
I often take taxis.
結 構タクシー乗っちゃう
Are you going to ride it?
乗っちゃうの?
Where does that kind of money come from?
そんな金どっから出てくるの?
It's really not in time for business.
本当に事業間に合わない
I see.
なるほど
I think so, but yeah.
と思うけど、 うん
If it was only about 30 minutes away, I would just walk.
30分くらいの距離だったら、 全然歩いていっちゃう
Is that so?
そうなの?
It's cute.
かわいいね
Do you often get called cute?
よくかわいいって言われる?
But, if you go to a rhinoceros shop or an izakaya,
だけどさ、ライミン屋とかさ、 居酒屋とか行ったらさ、
Especially in izakaya (Japanese pubs), there's always alcohol in it.
特に居酒屋とかだけどさ、 やっぱアルコール入ってるじゃん
At a pub, at that time...
居酒屋とかってさ、 その時にさ、
What do you say?
なんて言うの?
No, your sister is cute.
いや、お姉ちゃんかわいい
Sister, don't you know not to drink?
お姉ちゃん飲みなよってわかんない?
It is said.
言われる
That's what I'm told.
言われるよね
Your sister asks you to drink with her, right?
お姉ちゃん一緒に飲もうよって言われるでしょ?
That's what I'm told.
言われますね
What do you say then?
その時なんて言うの?
Are you saying okay?
いいよって言うの?
I can't drink alcohol.
お酒飲めないんで
That's right.
そうだよね
I guess I can't drink alcohol.
お酒飲めないとしたもんね
Have you ever had alcohol?
お酒飲んだことあるの?
Yeah.
うん
Do you like it a little?
ちょっと好き?
not at all.
全然
Don't you like it?
好きじゃない?
Too weak.
弱すぎて
She's a nice girl, and a cute girl.
いい女だし、かわいい女だね
Then.
そ したらね
There are more girls who are weak drinkers than girls who are strong drinkers.
お酒強い女の子より弱い女の子のほうが
I personally like my uncle.
おじさんは個人的には好きだよ
Yes, but.
そう、でも
So I wanted to do something about it.
よってどうにかしちゃいたいなって
With the help of alcohol.
お酒の力借りてね
I think I'd like to drink it.
飲みたいなーって思うけど
I see.
なるほどね
Do you like it?
好きなの?
I like it.
好 きー
copper?
どう?
Do you listen to the voice?
声に乗る?
I've never ridden one though.
乗ったことないけど
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's like the popoless that came.
来たポッポレスみたいな
Amazing.
すごー
I want to check it out.
チェックしたいな
What did you do?
何やった?
Not much.
あんまりね
あんまり
My car is enough.
うちに車で十分だね
That may be so.
それはそうかもしれない
Hey, can I ask you a naughty question?
ちょっとさ、 エッチな質問をしてっていい?
It's a naughty shoot after all.
やっぱりエッチな撮影じゃん
I was made to care about that.
そのこと気にしてもらった
I can't help it.
ちょっとしょうがないからさ
That's a naughty question.
エッチな質問っていうかさ
That's it though.
あれ だけどさ
You said you've never had a boyfriend.
彼氏できたことないって言ったじゃん
When was the last time you did it?
最後やったのいつあるの?
What's the last one?
最後 は?
Yeah.
うん
Eh, but like this...
え、でもこう...
At this time?
この時?
I see.
なるほどね
It was quite a while ago.
だいぶ前ですね
How many people have experience?
経験人数は何?
The number of experienced people is...
経験人数は...
both hands?
両手?
Both legs?
両足?
one hand?
片手?
Really?
ホントに?
Really, really.
ホ ントにホントに
I see.
そっか
No way.
まさかのね
I was told that you would be able to perform at my house.
うちに出演していただけるということで
I got such a cute girl.
こんな可愛い子ゲットしたって
Well, it's one handed.
え、片手なんだ
By the way, at that time.
ちなみにさ、 その時にさ
I finally did it.
最後やったさ
what?
何?
When you were in high school?
高校生の時?
I mean, I did it.
やったっていうのはさ
Boyfriend at the time?
当時の彼氏?
boyfriend.
彼氏
Are you only with your boyfriend?
彼氏としかやんないの?
I only do it with my boyfriend.
彼氏としかやらない
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Have you never been with anyone other than your boyfriend?
彼氏以外ってやったことないの?
I wonder if there is.
ないかなー
Well, it's the first time today, isn't it?
ないのにじゃあ今日初めてだよね
Is it okay to think of him as my boyfriend?
彼氏だと思っていいのかな?
Whatever.
なんなら
Is that what it is?
そういうことなのかな?
It seems like that's what happened.
そういうことでもなったそうだね
Look at your face.
顔を見たらね
Hmm.
う ーん
Really?
ほんっか
So how many uncles are you today?
じゃあ今日おじさんで何人目なんだろう?
Really?
本当に?
Why why why?
なんでなんでなんで?
Really?
本当に?
ほんとか
You look like an adult when you're 18 years old.
18歳にしたら大人っぽいよね
yes?
そう?
Is that so?
そうなの?
I don't know.
わかんない
Well, you know, I thought you were cute the moment I met you.
まあ、あの、 会った瞬間にかわいいっていうのはもつたわった
There was great excitement, and people talked about being a good girl.
大興があって、いい子っていうのもつたわった
Hey, then, you took a little walk.
やいちゃん、そしたらさ、 ちょっと散歩かかれたね
Not even?
さえない?
a little bit?
ちょっと?
Do you want to take a break while going to the aquarium?
水族館行っていたらちょっと休憩する?
Yeah.
うん
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I did it once.
一回しちゃった
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It was embarrassing, a little bit.
恥ずかしかったね、ちょっとね
Are you injured?
怪我は?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm glad you weren't hurt.
怪我しなくてよかった
What if I was told that I was injured and couldn't shoot?
怪我して撮影できませんなんて言われたらさ
No, it's okay.
いや、大丈夫
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
At my feet.
足元ね
It's not that bad though.
そんな悪くないけどね
Because it's a bump.
ぶつだからね
How many centimeters tall?
身長何センチ?
154 in.
154イン
Your weight is around 30kg, right?
体重30キロ台でしょ?
That's not true.
そんなことない
Really?
本当に?
How many cup breasts?
おっぱい何カップ?
D cup breasts.
おっぱいのDカップ
D cup?
Dカップ?
nice.
いいね
Well, that's my ex-boyfriend.
じゃああれ、今までの彼氏だったり
Well, I don't know if it's true or not.
まあ、本当かどうか分かんないけどね
Also a boyfriend.
彼氏っていうのも
Really?
本当 に?
I get compliments from men.
男性の人にさ、 なんか褒められるところ
Do you get praised?
褒められる?
I get praised for my body.
体で褒められる
I already know that you have a cute face.
顔可愛いってのはもう分かったから
Other than the face.
顔以外
With your neck?
首で?
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみだね
kana?
かな?
So, are you confident in yourself?
じゃあ、自分で自信がある?
Are you confident in yourself?
自分で自信がある?
Oh, maybe it's my neck.
あ、僕首でかも
Good, good.
いいね、いいね
I'm pretty confident that the neck is fine.
首でいいのは結構自信あるんだね
It's okay, it's okay.
いいじゃん、いいじゃん
Also, I wonder if I can do the butt as well.
あと、お尻もやれるかな
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみだね
I want to see it right away.
今すぐに見たいけど
Well, that can't be the case.
まあ、そういうわけにもいかないからね
cute.
可愛い
cute?
可愛い?
Did you have a dog?
犬飼ってたの?
Of course you're home now, right?
今もちろん実家でしょ?
Are you living there?
暮らしてるの?
Yeah.
うん
Do you have a dog at home and dance with it?
実家で犬とか飼って踊るんですか?
I have a cat now.
今、猫飼って
Keep it.
飼って
I've always had a dog since I was little.
小さい頃からずっとワンちゃんがいて、
My previous child passed away, so now I have a cat.
前の子が亡くなったから、 今、猫
Are you a cat or a dog?
猫と犬どっちですか?
Wow!
うわー!
うわーなんだ
I like them both.
ど っちも好きなんだ
I like both.
どっちも好き
I may not have one.
飼ってないかもしれない
Seriously?
まじか
I'm a little tired.
ちょっと疲れたね
If you're 18 years old, what do you play?
18歳はさ、 何して遊ぶの?
What do you do on your day off?
休みの日何にしてんの?
Do you go to your house on your day off?
休みの日、 家に行くってやつするかな?
But, like going out to eat, well...
でも、ご飯食べに行ったりとか、 まあ、
Eat dinner, grab some puri, go to karaoke,
ご飯食べて、プリ取って、 カラオケ行って、
Like.
みたいな
Like bowling.
ボーリングとか
I see.
なるほどね
A movie?
映画とか?
I should have gone to Spocha or something.
スポッチャとか行けばよかったね
ス ポ ッチャとか行けばよかったね
It's not like I'm really good at singing.
そんな、めちゃめちゃ 歌得意ってわけじゃないから
What were you doing in club activities?
部活、何かしてたの?
My club is cheerleading.
部活は、チア
dance?
ダンス?
Dancing, ok.
ダンス、まあまあまあ
Cheer?
チア?
Like the cheer squad.
チア部みたいな
Cheer club?
チア部?
Like play play.
プレイプレイとか
Ah, that's right.
ああ、そうだね
Supporting baseball.
野球応援とか
I have that image.
そういうイメージがあって
Wow!
わ ー!
thank you.
ありがとうございます
What did you ask for?
何頼んだの?
Tweet!
ツ イ!
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
Dangerous!
危 ない!
It's dangerous.
危ないね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
What did you ask for?
何頼んだの?
Beef skewers?
牛串?
sorry.
すみません
す みません
Beef skewers?
牛串?
Looks delicious.
おいしそうだね
You can eat it.
食べていいよ
It's so scary.
めっちゃ怖い
copper?
どう?
delicious?
おいしい?
It's insanely delicious.
めちゃめちゃおいしい
Ah, I ate it.
あ、食べた
It's really delicious, but I'll eat it.
めちゃめちゃおいしいけど、食べるね
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
That's nice.
いいですね
good?
いい?
delicious?
おいしい?
happiness?
幸せ?
That was good.
良かったね
It's insanely delicious.
めちゃめちゃおいしい
That's what a good woman is.
いい女はあれだね
This is a picture of me eating it.
食べるときの絵になるね
Didn't you go?
行かなかった?
I won't go.
行かない
Did you enjoy the walk?
散歩楽しかった?
it was fun.
楽しかった
it was fun?
楽しかった?
I also ate some delicious food.
美味しいものも食べたしね
It was insanely delicious.
めちゃめちゃ美味しかった
Thank you for the meal.
ごちそうさまでしたということで
Yes, thank you for the meal.
はい、ごちそうさまでした
Thank you for the meal.
ごちそうさまでしたということで
Well then, just a little.
じゃあ、ちょっとね
I guess the tension has eased, too.
緊張もほぐれて、かな
yes.
はい
Go to the hotel.
ホ テル行って
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
yes.
はい
So shall we go to the hotel?
それでホテル行こうか
Well then, yai-chan.
じゃあ、やいちゃん
You came to the hotel.
ホテル来たね
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
Also.
また
Be nervous.
緊張してね
so?
そんなに?
Just ate something delicious.
さっき美味しいもの食べてさ
I don't feel like eating it, but just a little.
食べやる気じゃないけど、ちょっとさ
Eat it.
食べてさ
Take a walk.
散歩してさ
I've heard a lot of things.
ちょっといろいろ聞いてきたじゃん
I feel like this is a good place to talk.
おしゃべりはこんなとこでいいかなって感じでさ
I've also heard that it has a good neck.
首レがいいっていうのも聞いたし
What is that?
その何?
Butt?
お尻?
I feel a little more confident.
もうちょっと自信ありますと
Yeah.
うん
My butt...
お尻が...
Well.
まぁ
I see.
なるほどね
That's it.
それでさ
Hurry up and stop talking like this.
早くこんなおしゃべりよりさ
It just gets a little messy.
ちょっと ビッタリになるだけだからさ
There's no reason I'm thinking of taking a naughty photo shoot.
エッチな撮影しようかなと思うわけもさ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
yes.
はい
yeah?
ん?
No, no.
いやいや
it was fun?
楽しかった?
The walk was fun.
散歩楽しかったですね
it was fun?
楽 しかった?
What were you doing on your walk?
散 歩して、何してたんですか?
What were you doing?
何してた?
Go for a walk.
散歩行って
Go for a walk and eat vegetables.
散歩行って、 野菜の
Did you eat vegetables?
野菜やったの?
Eat your vegetables, eat your vegetables, eat your vegetables.
野菜やって、 野菜食べて、 野菜食べて
What did you eat?
何食べたの?
Hmm, I ate that.
うーんと、 あれ食べましたね
yes.
はい
Beef salt.
牛肉塩
Beef salt?
牛肉塩?
copper?
どう?
I also ate apple candy.
りんご飴でも食べましたね
If you think it's cute, it's not.
可愛くていいって思ったらそうじゃないんだよ
I ate a lot of meat.
結構がっつり肉食べました
Wasn't it delicious?
美味しかったな?
Yeah.
うん
It was cute though.
可愛いでしたけど
Yeah?
うん?
Already?
もうですか?
Haven't you taken a walk yet?
まだ散歩しなかった?
No, not at all.
いや、全然
Is it okay?
いいの?
Have you taken a walk in this outfit?
この格好で散歩してきた?
It might be cold though.
寒いかもしれないけど
This look is a little off.
この格好はちょっと
Okay?
いいか?
I'm doing some work around the house.
家の中わざしてる
Take it slow.
ゆっくりで
slowly.
ゆ っくり
Is it okay?
いいの?
A fairy-like tea bag.
妖精的にティーバックに
what happened?
どう したの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Don't put your hands on it.
手をかけちゃダメだ
Just give it to me.
手にしてあげてほら
Even you can hold it like this.
自分でさえこうやって抱えてほら
It's spread out properly.
ちゃんと広げてるの
No, no, no.
ダメダメ
The person who took it is no good.
取った人じゃダメ
Something's starting to bite into me.
なんか食い込んでくるの
That's no good.
ダメじゃん
Try expanding it yourself from here.
こっちからで一回自分で広げてみて
Let me expand it myself.
自分で広げてみせて
Don't scratch it with your fingers.
指でかくちゃダメだ
What are you doing?
何するの?
do not.
しない
I don't.
しないんだ
absolutely?
全く?
Does that mean you don't have to?
する必要はないってこと?
different.
違う
No.
違うよ
what?
何?
do not.
しない
Aren't you horny?
ムラムラしない?
do not.
しない
I'm so horny right now.
今すごいムラムラしてる
now.
今
Just spread it out a little bit.
ちょっとそのまま広げててね
Of course you don't use this?
こんなもちろん使わないの?
You can try it yourself.
自分でくりじってみてもいいんだよ
I have to use it.
使わないと
This is my first time.
初めてこれ
It started to move around.
くねくね動き出しちゃった
I forgot about it myself.
自分でくねくねし忘れちゃった
what happened?
どう したの?
Is it really in your chest?
めっちゃ胸に入ってるの?
Noisy?
うるしい?